- Problem?
- No.
l think the Reverend Hofstadter
is making an ironic connection...
(Sheldon:)...between your statement
about love...
(Sheldon:)...and your rejection of his proposal
in the bedroom.
(Penny:)Oh, grow up.
- Hey, I didn't say it.
- That's enough.
- Well, he started it.
- Well, I'm ending it.
"Bernadette, I wanna thank you for
allowing me to be your maid of honor.
l also want you to know
that I will be happy to do it again...
...if this marriage craps out."
(Leonard:)Thank you, Amy. Very touching.
"Howard and Bernadette...
(Leonard:)...you are lucky enough
to be best friends who love each other.
(Leonard:)And that's the strongest kind of love,
because at its core...
(Leonard:)...it has kindness, patience
and respect."
(Leonard:)Qualities that are hard to find
in people these days.